<resources>
    <string name="app_name">HapyBdayMachi</string>
    <string name="openBdayGift">Open Bday Gift Machi</string>


    <string name="q1">Walking with a friend in the Night is better than walking alone in the Day light</string>
    <string name="q2">Good friends R hard to find, difficult to leave, impossible to forget</string>
    <string name="q3">Life is a party whenever I\'m with you. You turn my tears into smiles when we share and laugh togetherl</string>
    <string name="q4">A true friend is someone who never gets tried of listening to your pointless dramas over and over again</string>
    <string name="q5">A good friend would bail you out of jail but your best friend would be the one sitting next to you saying, damn that was cool</string>
    <string name="q6">Relation of friendship is greater then the relation of blood</string>
    <string name="q7">Every friendship doesn\'t change into love but every love begins with friendship</string>
    <string name="q8">A friend is a person who goes around saying nice things about you beside your back</string>
    <string name="q9">Good friends are like starts. You don\'t always see them but you know they\'re always there</string>
    <string name="q10">If friendship is your weakest point then your the strongest person in the world</string>
    <string name="q11">World is full of smiles, whenever friends are with me</string>
    <string name="q12">Friendship isn\'t a big thing it\'s a million little things</string>
    <string name="q13">That awesome moment when you\'re telling a lie and your best friend notices and joins you</string>
    <string name="q14">A true friend reaches for your hand and touches your hear</string>
    <string name="q15">A true friend sees the first tear, catches the second an stops the third</string>
    <string name="q16">A best friend is like a four leaf cover. Hard to find and luck to have</string>
    <string name="q17">Friends are notes to life\'s great songs. A melody that carries you along</string>
    <string name="q18">A friend is someone who gives you total freedom to be yourself</string>
    <string name="q19">Nice friendship is like the breathing air, you will never see it but you will always feel its presence</string>
    <string name="q20">What is a Best friend? A single soul in two bodies</string>
    <string name="q21">A friend is someone who can see the truth and pain in you even when you are fooling everyone else</string>
    <string name="q22">Good friends will share the umbrella. Best friends Will steal it and yell: RUN LOSER RUN!</string>
    <string name="q23">Friendship is the only cement that will ever hold the world together</string>
    <string name="q24">Your friendship to me means a lot to me</string>
    <string name="back">Back</string>
</resources>
